petsbest.com 2007-02-24

# PestBest.com Privacy Policy

This Web site is owned by Pets Best Insurance Services, and its affiliates ("Pets Best").

Pets Best provides unconditional Internet access only and does not control any third-party material from authorized or unauthorized externally linked Web sites to Pets Best's Web sites. Pets Best shall not be liable for the content or accuracy of information located on any such externally-linked Web pages.

##  Privacy Policy Statement

###  HOW WE PROTECT AND USE CUSTOMER INFORMATION

We safeguard the security and integrity of customer information. We are committed to protecting the security and integrity of customer information through procedures and technology designed for this purpose. For example: We limit employee access to customer information to those who have a business reason to know this information. Employees are required to honor our code of conduct, which includes standards to protect customer confidentiality. They are subject to disciplinary action if they fail to do so. We maintain policies and procedures covering the proper physical security of workplaces and records. Our physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards meet or exceed federal standards regarding the protection of customer information. We require independent contractors and outside companies who work with us to adhere to strict privacy standards through their contracts with us. 

We use technological means (such as backup files, virus detection and eradication software, firewalls, and other computer software and hardware) to protect against unauthorized access or alterations to customer data.

Pets Best has prepared the following Privacy Policy Statement to describe our policy regarding Pets Best's collection, storage and use of information which our Web site visitors may transmit to Pets Best while visiting our site.

**_Pets Best can be reached via e-mail for any questions regarding this web site or the privacy policy at: webmaster@petsbest.com, or by regular mail at the following postal address. If you prefer that we not disclose nonpublic personal information about you to nonaffiliated third parties, you may opt out of those disclosures (that is, you may direct us to not make any disclosures except as we may otherwise be authorized by law). If you wish to opt out of these disclosures, you may contact us at the e-mail address listed above or by regular mail at the following address:_**

Pets Best Insurance Services 2710 Sunrise Rim Road, Suite 100 Boise, Idaho 83705 Attn: Web Master 

For each visitor to our Web site ("User"), our Web server will automatically recognize the User's domain name, but not the User's e-mail address. Pets Best collects and stores the domain name, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, the aggregate information on the Web pages that Users access or visit, and any and all information volunteered by the User, such as survey information and/or information we seek for site registration or security purposes including information entered by the User for policy applications including financial information. We will keep financial information (such as credit card and bank account information) in our files for future billing of policy premiums as agreed to by the User when applying for policies. The User information collected by Pets Best will not be shared with organizations which are not affiliated with Pets Best unless otherwise noted below. 

Users who supply us with their postal address, e-mail address or telephone numbers on-line can expect Pets Best to share that information with Pets Best's affiliates, its agents or brokers. As such, these Users may receive periodic mailings from Pets Best, its affiliates, its agents or brokers with information regarding new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please indicate this choice in your on-line communication and Pets Best will remove your name from the list it shares with its affiliates, its agents or brokers. 

Pets Best places Internet cookies on our Users' hard drives. A cookie is a small file that is sent from Pets Best's Web server to a Users' personal computer. This file contains information about a User's visit to Pets Best's Web site that only Pets Best's server can read. The cookies are stored on the User's hard drive and are not stored, in any form, by Pets Best. Pets Best uses only session cookies and not persistent cookies. Information derived from reading the cookie is stored by Pets Best and is protected under the terms of Pets Best's corporate data privacy/security policy. Cookies are used to enhance a User's return visit to Pets Best's Web site. Users may decline the cookies by using the appropriate feature of their Web browser software, but by doing so, may experience a decrease in functionality. When applicable, cookies are used to verify the User's authorization to access certain Pets Best Web pages (e.g., a Userâ€™s access to policy information or maintenance of User information). 

The information you provide to us online is protected by Secure Socket Layer (SSL technology). SSL is the leading security protocol for data transfer on the Internet. This technology scrambles your account information as it moves between your PC's browser and Pets Best's computer systems. When information is scrambled, or encrypted in this way, it becomes nearly impossible for anyone other than Pets Best to read it. This secure session helps protect the safety and confidentiality of your information. From our web sites, we do not knowingly collect or use personal information from children under 13 without containing verifiable consent from their parents. Should a child whom we know to be under 13 send personal information to us, we will only use that information to respond directly to that child, seek parental consent, or provide parental notice. We are not responsible for the data collection and use practices of nonaffiliated third parties to which our web sites may link.

For more information about the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), visit the FTC web site: www.ftc.gov.

###  Copyright Notice

All service marks and logos located on Pets Best's Web sites are owned by Pets Best unless otherwise indicated. Removal or reproduction, by any means, of any logo, trademark, service mark, copyrighted material or the name of Pets Best or its affiliates, is expressly prohibited without the prior written consent of Pets Best. All materials located on Pets Best's Web Sites are protected by United States copyright laws and all other applicable laws. 

© 2006 Pets Best Insurance Services. All rights reserved.

###  E-mail Notice

Except as required by privacy laws, if User elects to communicate with Pets Best via Internet e-mail, the User acknowledges that the information contained in the User's message shall not be considered confidential and that Pets Best shall be free to disclose such information contained therein without any liability or limitation.
